Solidarity Committee of the Capital District; Records apap042
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Subject Files, 1978-2000; 3; 13.8 cubic ft.
  - Salt Miners' Strike, 1986 (Box 26 (3-Subject Files), Folder 10)
  - Save Our Cities, 1992 (Box 26 (3-Subject Files), Folder 11)
  - Schenectady, 1995 (Box 26 (3-Subject Files), Folder 12)
  - Schenectady Trash, 1996 (Box 26 (3-Subject Files), Folder 13)
  - Sealy Mattress, Undated (Box 27 (3-Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - Service Employee International Union, 1984-1985 (Box 27 (3-Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - Siena College Speech about Mergers, 1987 (Box 27 (3-Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - Slate Workers' Strike, Undated (Box 27 (3-Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - Solidarity, 1989-1993 (Box 27 (3-Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - Solidarnosc, 1988 (Box 27 (3-Subject Files), Folder 6)
  - Social Security Reform, 1998 (Box 27 (3-Subject Files), Folder 7)
  - South Africa, Flyers, Pamphlets, 1984-1986 (Box 27 (3-Subject Files), Folder 8)
  - South Africa, 1980-1984 (Box 27 (3-Subject Files), Folder 9)
  - South Africa, 1985-1988 (Box 27 (3-Subject Files), Folder 10)
  - South Africa, News Clippings, 1983-1984 (Box 28 (3-Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - South Africa, News Clippings, 1985 (Box 28 (3-Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - South Africa, News Clippings, 1986; 1987 (Box 28 (3-Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - Supermarket Workers and the Teamsters, 1984-1988 (Box 28 (3-Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - Sweatshops, 1996-1997 (Box 28 (3-Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - "Testimony of the Union Procedures and Programmers Network", 1991 (Box 28 (3-Subject Files), Folder 6)
  - Transamerica Coalition for Bargaining Strength, 1985 (Box 28 (3-Subject Files), Folder 7)
  - Transit Workers Strike, 1985 (Box 28 (3-Subject Files), Folder 8)
  - Troy Housing Authority, 1993 (Box 28 (3-Subject Files), Folder 9)
  - TWA Strike, International Federation of Flight Attendants, 1985-1987 (Box 28 (3-Subject Files), Folder 10)
  - UE SuperSteel, 1994-1995 (Box 28 (3-Subject Files), Folder 11)
  - Union Made Product Directory, 1998 (Box 28 (3-Subject Files), Folder 12)
  - Unions and the High Performance Workplace, 1993 (Box 29 (3-Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - Unions Struggles, 1991-1992 (Box 29 (3-Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - Union Farm Workers, Grape Boycott, 1984-1987 (Box 29 (3-Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - Union Farm Workers, Grape Boycott, 1988 (Box 29 (3-Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - Union Farm Workers, Grape Boycott, 1989 (Box 29 (3-Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - Union Farm Workers, Grape Boycott, 1990-1995 (Box 29 (3-Subject Files), Folder 6)
  - Union Farm Workers, Grape Boycott, News Clippings, 1988 (Box 29 (3-Subject Files), Folder 7)
  - Union Farm Workers, Grape Boycott, News Clippings, 1989 (Box 30 (3-Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - Union Farm Workers, Grape Boycott, News Clippings, 1990-1991 (Box 30 (3-Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - Union Farm Workers, Grape Boycott, Flyers, Undated (Box 30 (3-Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - Union Farm Workers, Grape Boycott, Food and Justice, 1987-1988 (Box 30 (3-Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - Union Farm Workers, Grape Boycott, "The Impact of Pesticides used on California Table Grapes on Farmers, Consumers and the Environment", 1989 (Box 30 (3-Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - Union Farm Workers, Grape Boycott, News from UFW, 1898-1990 (Box 30 (3-Subject Files), Folder 6)
  - Union Farm Workers, Grape Boycott, Undated (Box 30 (3-Subject Files), Folder 7)
  - United Paper Workers International Union, Local 871 against Tagsons Paper, 1982 (Box 30 (3-Subject Files), Folder 8)
  - United Paper Workers International Union, Strike in Rumford, ME, 1986 (Box 30 (3-Subject Files), Folder 9)
  - United Paper Workers International Union, Strike against International Paper Co., 1987-1988 (Box 30 (3-Subject Files), Folder 10)
  - United Paper Workers International Union, 1992-1993 (Box 31 (3-Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - United Paper Workers International Union, Local 1478, South Glens Falls Encore Paper Strike, 1985 (Box 31 (3-Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - United Parcel Service, 1997 (Box 31 (3-Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - United Staff Union Constitution, 1991 (Box 31 (3-Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - United Steelworkers of America, District, "Building Your Steelworkers Local", 1993 (Box 31 (3-Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - United Steelworkers of America, Local 3701, Local News, 1991-1993 (Box 31 (3-Subject Files), Folder 6)
  - United University Professions, 1983-1993 (Box 31 (3-Subject Files), Folder 7)
  - University at Albany Field House Construction, 1989 (Box 31 (3-Subject Files), Folder 8)
  - The Vermont Job Gap, Phase I, Basic Needs and a Livable Wage, 1997 (Box 31 (3-Subject Files), Folder 9)
  - Video Display Terminals and Safety, 1984-1986 (Box 31 (3-Subject Files), Folder 10)
  - Viviano Macaroni, 1984 (Box 31 (3-Subject Files), Folder 11)
  - Weekly Federal Employees' News Digest, 1988-1990 (Box 31 (3-Subject Files), Folder 12)
  - Welfare Warriors, 1995-1997 (Box 31 (3-Subject Files), Folder 13)
  - WMHT Organizing, National Association of Broadcast Employees and Technicians, 1985-1986 (Box 31 (3-Subject Files), Folder 14)
  - WMHT Organizing, National Association of Broadcast Employees and Technicians, 1985-1987 (Box 31 (3-Subject Files), Folder 15)
  - Workers Rights Board, Public Hearing on Workfare, 1997 (Box 32 (3-Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - Workfare, 1995-1997 (Box 32 (3-Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - Workfare, Public Hearing, March 11, 1997 (Box 32 (3-Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - Working USA, 1998 (Box 32 (3-Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - World Food Day, Albany, 1983 (Box 32 (3-Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - World Food Day, Churning, 1988 (Box 32 (3-Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - WRGB TV, Channel 6 Technicians' Strike, 1984 May-1984 June (Box 32 (3-Subject Files), Folder 6)
  - Zinc Miners' Strike, United Steelworkers of America, Local 3701, Newsletter, 1986-1989 (Box 32 (3-Subject Files), Folder 7)
  - Zinc Miners' Strike, United Steelworkers of America, Local 3701, 1988-1989 (Box 32 (3-Subject Files), Folder 8)
  - Zinc Miners' Strike, St. Lawrence County, 1985-1989 (Box 32 (3-Subject Files), Folder 9)
  - Zinc Miners' Rally, 1988 December 3 (Box 32 (3-Subject Files), Folder 10)
  - 1st Solidarity Pledge Drive, 1987 (Box 33 (3-Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - Activist Directory (By Campus Action), 1992 September (Box 33 (3-Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - AFSCME: Civil Rights Work, 1989 (Box 33 (3-Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - AFSCME: Native American Union Projects, 1994-1998 (Box 33 (3-Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - Agriculture- New York State, 1979-1995 (Box 33 (3-Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - Akwesasne: St. Regis Casinos & Police Standoff, 1990 (Box 33 (3-Subject Files), Folder 6)
  - Akwesasne: St. Regis Casinos & Police Standoff - Press Clippings, 1990 (Box 33 (3-Subject Files), Folder 7)
  - Akwesasne Union- Mohawk Nation, 1990-1994 (Box 33 (3-Subject Files), Folder 8)
  - Albany Community Land Trust: Appeal to NY Telephone, 1991 (Box 33 (3-Subject Files), Folder 9)
  - Albany County Central Federation of Labor - Solidarity Challenge, 1990 (Box 33 (3-Subject Files), Folder 10)
  - Albany Public Library: Blizzard Closings, 1993 (Box 33 (3-Subject Files), Folder 11)
  - Amalgamated Bank of New York 60th Anniversary Packet, 1983 (Box 33 (3-Subject Files), Folder 12)
  - American Labor Museum: Botto House, 1985 (Box 33 (3-Subject Files), Folder 13)
  - A. Philip Randolph Institute: National Background & Albany, NY Chapter Activity, 1979-1990 (Box 33 (3-Subject Files), Folder 14)
  - Attica: Analysis of Conditions in NYS Prisons, 1982 (Box 33 (3-Subject Files), Folder 15)
  - BE&K Construction Campaign, 1994 (Box 33 (3-Subject Files), Folder 16)
  - Bovine Growth Hormone (BGH), 1994 (Box 33 (3-Subject Files), Folder 17)
  - California Grape Boycott, 1990-1992 (Box 34 (3-Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - Capital District Coalition for Southern Africa & Against Racism, 1995 (Box 34 (3-Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - Capital District Labor- Religion Coalition: 8th Annual Awards Dinner, 2005 (Box 34 (3-Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - Capital District Minority Workers Campaign, 1992 (Box 34 (3-Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - Caterpillar Rally, 1993 (Box 34 (3-Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - Central America Democracy Rights, 1990 (Box 34 (3-Subject Files), Folder 6)
  - Child Labor Issues (Local & National Involvement), 1995-1999 (Box 34 (3-Subject Files), Folder 7)
  - Citizens Environmental Coalition: Meeting Minutes, 04/25/1993 (Box 34 (3-Subject Files), Folder 8)
  - Citizens for a Clean Environment- Family Farm Rights, 2000 (Box 34 (3-Subject Files), Folder 9)
  - Citizens Utility Board Rally, 1994 (Box 34 (3-Subject Files), Folder 10)
  - Communications Workers of America vs. AT&T, 1992 (Box 34 (3-Subject Files), Folder 11)
  - Community Canning & Food Preservation, 1988 (Box 34 (3-Subject Files), Folder 12)
  - Community Services Society: Bronx, 1995 (Box 34 (3-Subject Files), Folder 13)
  - Coors Boycott, 1987 (Box 34 (3-Subject Files), Folder 14)
  - DECERT Local 424: Issues with Rival Unions, 1994-1995 (Box 34 (3-Subject Files), Folder 15)
  - Drug Testing Issues, 1988 (Box 34 (3-Subject Files), Folder 16)
  - Earthwise Education Center, ca. 1992 (Box 34 (3-Subject Files), Folder 17)
  - East Timor Action Network, 1993-1995 (Box 34 (3-Subject Files), Folder 18)
  - Economic Conversion Coalition: Economic Diversity Conferences, 1989-1990 (Box 34 (3-Subject Files), Folder 19)
  - Economic Conversion Coalition: NYS Defense Advisory Panel, 1990 (Box 34 (3-Subject Files), Folder 20)
  - Economic Conversion Coalition: U.S./Soviet Relations, 1987-1990 (Box 34 (3-Subject Files), Folder 21)
  - Economic Conversion Coalition: Watervliet Arsenal, 1990-1995 (Box 34 (3-Subject Files), Folder 22)
  - Employee Ownership Project (EOP) of Albany Region, 1979; 1985-1988 (Box 35 (3-Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - Employee Ownership Project (EOP) of Albany Region, 1989-1993 (Box 35 (3-Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - Enterprise Zones, 1982-1990 (Box 35 (3-Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - Environmentalists vs. Economic Developers, 1992; 1995 (Box 35 (3-Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - Farmworker Solidarity Network of NYS, 1989 (Box 35 (3-Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - Farmworker Solidarity Network of NYS, 1989 (Box 35 (3-Subject Files), Folder 6)
  - Farmworker Support Network, 1989-1995 (Box 35 (3-Subject Files), Folder 7)
  - Finch, Pruyn & Company Union Rebuttal, 1996 (Box 35 (3-Subject Files), Folder 8)
  - Focus on Farming Vol. VIII /#6, 1987 March 23-29 (Box 35 (3-Subject Files), Folder 9)
  - Funiciello, John: Eugene V. Debs Award (1984) & Jim Perry Progressive Leadership Award (1995), 1985 (Box 35 (3-Subject Files), Folder 10)
  - Funiciello, Theresa: Anti-Poverty Work, 1988-1990 (Box 35 (3-Subject Files), Folder 11)
  - General Agreement on Tariffs & Trade (GATT), 1994 (Box 36 (3-Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - General Electric Tax Assessment Fight & Layoffs, 1992-1995 (Box 36 (3-Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - Great Law Documentary (Linda Tokarchuk), 1990-1992 (Box 36 (3-Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - Greenway Council of Hudson River Valley: River Compact, 1990 (Box 36 (3-Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - Hunger Issues:Food Monitor, 1982 July-1982 December; 1983 March-1983 April; 1983 July-1983 August (Box 36 (3-Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - Hunger Issues New York State, 1980-1992 (Box 36 (3-Subject Files), Folder 6)
  - Illegal Immigrant Cases, 1999 February-1999 March (Box 36 (3-Subject Files), Folder 7)
  - Industrial Cooperative Association - National Center for Employee Ownership, 1984-1989 (Box 36 (3-Subject Files), Folder 8)
  - Infant Formula Action Coalition, 1990-1992 (Box 36 (3-Subject Files), Folder 9)
  - Israeli Institute for Military Studies: Arab-Israeli Peace Process, 1990 (Box 36 (3-Subject Files), Folder 10)
    Contains letter to John Funiciello from Jimmy Carter.
  - James Bay II: Hydro-Quebec Costs, 1993 Fall (Box 36 (3-Subject Files), Folder 11)
  - James Bay II: Innu Nation Rights, 1992-1993 (Box 36 (3-Subject Files), Folder 12)
  - James Bay II: Update by P.R.O.J.E.C.T., Inc., 02/1993 (Box 36 (3-Subject Files), Folder 13)
  - Jobs with Justice: Official Union with SCCD, 1995 (Box 37 (3-Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - Jones, Mary Harris "Mother": Stamp Resolution, 1994 March (Box 37 (3-Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - Korean Labor Unions Bulk, 1984-1985 (Box 37 (3-Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - Labor Action Coalition of New York, 1982-1983 (Box 37 (3-Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - Labor Party Advocates, 1993-1996 (Box 37 (3-Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - Labor Research Association:Economic Notes, 1983 September-1985 August (Box 37 (3-Subject Files), Folder 6)
    issues missing.
  - Laborers' International Union, 1980-1981 (Box 37 (3-Subject Files), Folder 7)
  - Leaflets: Types of Union Support, ca. 1981 (Box 37 (3-Subject Files), Folder 8)
  - Levi's Boycott/Fuerza Unida, 1991-1994 (Box 37 (3-Subject Files), Folder 9)
  - Lucy, William: Photo & Brief Background, Undated (Box 37 (3-Subject Files), Folder 10)
  - Martin Luther King Jr. Celebrations, 2001-2002 (Box 37 (3-Subject Files), Folder 11)
  - McEntee, Gerald W. (AFSCME President), 1981-1990 (Box 37 (3-Subject Files), Folder 12)
  - Minimum Wage Lawsuit, 1995 (Box 37 (3-Subject Files), Folder 13)
  - National Center for the Laity: Initiatives & Correspondence, 1984-1989 (Box 37 (3-Subject Files), Folder 14)
  - National Commission for Democracy in Mexico, 1992-1995 (Box 37 (3-Subject Files), Folder 15)
  - National Commission for Democracy in Mexico - Cecelia Rodriguez Visit to Albany, 1996 (Box 37 (3-Subject Files), Folder 16)
  - National Labor Committee: NAFTA Concerns, 1993 (Box 37 (3-Subject Files), Folder 17)
  - Navajo Preference in Employment Act, 1994 (Box 37 (3-Subject Files), Folder 18)
  - New York Civil Liberties Union, 1986-1992 (Box 38 (3-Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - New York COMPACT Agreement, 1986 (Box 38 (3-Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - NY Minimum Wage Action, 1993-1996 (Box 38 (3-Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - New York Solidarity By-Laws& Mission Statement, 1991 (Box 38 (3-Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - New York State Commission on Lobbying Guidelines, 1998 (Box 38 (3-Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - Nepotism Issues, 1990 (Box 38 (3-Subject Files), Folder 6)
  - Newsletter Collection-National Samples, 1982-1997 (Box 38 (3-Subject Files), Folder 7)
  - Newsletters: How-to/ Instructions, ca. 1994 (Box 38 (3-Subject Files), Folder 8)
  - Niebuhr Institute at Siena College, 1984 (Box 38 (3-Subject Files), Folder 9)
  - Ohio Family Farm Movement - AFSCME/NYS, 1986 (Box 38 (3-Subject Files), Folder 10)
  - OPEIU Local 2- Tie Vote/ Contract Ratification, 1992 (Box 38 (3-Subject Files), Folder 11)
  - Physicians Forum-Cooperation with Unions, 1990-1991 (Box 38 (3-Subject Files), Folder 12)
  - Printing Bids-Mohawk& Precision Graphics, 1988 April (Box 38 (3-Subject Files), Folder 13)
  - Prison Reform Issues, 1980-1982 (Box 38 (3-Subject Files), Folder 14)
  - Public Employees Federation, 1984-1997 (Box 38 (3-Subject Files), Folder 15)
  - Pyramid Lake Annual Meetings, 1995-1996 (Box 38 (3-Subject Files), Folder 16)
  - Riverspark Projects, 1985-1987 (Box 38 (3-Subject Files), Folder 17)
  - Rural Advancement Fund, 1983-1984 (Box 38 (3-Subject Files), Folder 18)
  - Rural Coalition Assembly, 1997 (Box 38 (3-Subject Files), Folder 19)
  - Schenectady: Economic Progess, 1995 Spring (Box 39 (3-Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - Self-Help & Resource Exchange (Share), ca. 1986-1997 (Box 39 (3-Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - September 19 Union, ca. 1988-1994 (Box 39 (3-Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - September 19 Union, ca. 1988-1994 (Box 39 (3-Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - Sierra Club: NYC Branch (John Klotz), 1993 (Box 39 (3-Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - Solidarity Annual Retreat, 2000 July; 2003 July (Box 39 (3-Subject Files), Folder 6)
  - Solidarity Committee - 25th Anniversary DVD, 2008 Fall (Box 39 (3-Subject Files), Folder 7)
  - Solidarity Committee Press Clippings, 1990-2000 (Box 39 (3-Subject Files), Folder 8)
  - Solidarity Day, 1981 September 19 (Box 39 (3-Subject Files), Folder 9)
  - Solidarity Day-AFSCME Songbook, 1981 (Box 40 (3-Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - Solidarity Day-Press Clippings, 1981 (Box 40 (3-Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - Solidarity Member Organizations, 1994 (Box 40 (3-Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - Solidarity Website Maintenance, 1996-1997 (Box 40 (3-Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - "Songs & Poems by Working People of Troy", ca. 1989 (Box 40 (3-Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - State of NY Commission of Investigation - Green Haven Correctional Facility, 1981 (Box 40 (3-Subject Files), Folder 6)
  - Student Association of the State University of New York, 1987 (Box 40 (3-Subject Files), Folder 7)
  - SUNY Graduate Students-Collective Bargaining, 1992 (Box 40 (3-Subject Files), Folder 8)
  - Troy Housing Authority, 1992 (Box 40 (3-Subject Files), Folder 9)
  - Troy Labor Center: Coalition for Jobs, Undated (Box 40 (3-Subject Files), Folder 10)
  - Tanzania Trade Unions, 1986-1994 (Box 40 (3-Subject Files), Folder 11)
  - Teamsters Local 284: Beer Wars, 1994 (Box 40 (3-Subject Files), Folder 12)
  - Teamsters Truck Strike, 1994 (Box 40 (3-Subject Files), Folder 13)
  - United Electrical 59th Annual Convention- Officers Report, 1994 (Box 40 (3-Subject Files), Folder 14)
  - United Farm Workers, 1993-1996 (Box 40 (3-Subject Files), Folder 15)
  - U.S.-Mexican Free Trade Agreement: Impact on NYS - J. Funiciello Testimony, 1992 (Box 40 (3-Subject Files), Folder 16)
  - Watertown Nurses' & Techs' Strike (SEIU Local 721), 1992 (Box 40 (3-Subject Files), Folder 17)
  - Workers' Rights Board, 1997-1998 (Box 40 (3-Subject Files), Folder 18)
  - "Wrongdoers Escape Act" -- Lobby Against Bill S.2277/A.4509, 1999 (Box 40 (3-Subject Files), Folder 19)
  - Youthbuild Act, 1990-1992 (Box 40 (3-Subject Files), Folder 20)
- Photographs, 1988-1993; 4; 0.2 cubic ft.
  The series contains photographs that help document the Solidarity Committee's involvement in the Greyhound strike, the laundry workers strike, The United Farm Workers "Wrath of Grapes" campaign, minimum wage, NAFTA, the environment, the Daily News Strike, Solidarity Day, Ravenswood, and the Teamsters. Also includes National Football League strike, legislative photos of Robert C. Byrd and John Conyers, Jr., and SCCD with Teamsters Local 72.
  Arranged alphabetically by subject.
  - Daily News Strike, 1990; 4.1 (Box 1 (4-Photographs), Folder 1)
    - Family Day on the Picket Line, 1990 December
      Striking copy editor Beverly Weintraub gives a ride to her three-year-old daughter Abigail on the picket line at the New York Daily News. Meanwhile, the New York police have refuted charges by publisher James Hoge that the 10 striking unions have conspired to "commit violence" against the newspaper as circulation plummeted and major advertisers dropped out. (25-1-90).
    - For a Fair Settlement, 1991 January 7
      New York Governor Mario Cuomo is applauded for calling for a fair settlement at the New York Daily News at a rally for strikers. Leading the applause are New York State AFL-CIO President Edward Cleary, Newspaper and Mail deliverers President Mike Alvino and ladies' Garment Workers President Jay Mazur. (1-1-91).
    - Rallying the Daily News Unions, 1990 November 12
      Union members and supporters, some 15,000 strong, rally strikers outside the New York Daily News building on 42nd Street. Represented by 10 unions, 3,000 employees of the third largest daily in the United States went on strike October 25. They had been working without contracts since March 31. Management brought in scabs immediately, but distribution of the paper is down sharply. (23-1-90).
  - Environment (Box 1 (4-Photographs), Folder 2)
    For a Balanced Solution.
    Trade unionists rally in Portland, Ore., to ease the economic plight of timber workers and their communities that the Bush administration had long ignored following a court order to halt cutting on federal lands to protect wildlife. President Clinton issued a directive to his cabinet to have a solution on his desk in two months. (8-4-93).
  - Football & Labor Issues, 1980s (Box 1 (4-Photographs), Folder 3)
    Two black and white photos depict a strike by National Football League players in the 1980s, though they do not specify if it is the 1982 or 1987 strike. (ID numbers on the photos may indicate 1987.) One picture shows the scab pick-up game between the Detroit Lions and Tampa Bay Buccaneers, while the other shows fans picketing with the real Washington Redskins. The third photo, which is also undated, depicts the New England Patriots' Mosi Tatupu striking with Ladies Garment Workers in Fall River, Massachusetts.
  - Grape Boycott & United Farm Workers, 1988-1992; 4.4 (Box 1 (4-Photographs), Folder 4)
    - Holding Fast, 1988
      Farm Workers President Cesar Chavez, in a water-only fast since July 17 to draw attention to labor's boycott of table grapes and the use of toxic chemicals by California growers, embraces his granddaughter Nicole during a mass in Delano, Calif. The union has pointed up the dangers of pesticides to farm workers and consumers. (34-1-88).
    - Farm Workers Protest
      Farm Workers President Cesar Chavez (center; Dolores Huerta, right) took the UFW's demand on five hazardous pesticides to the steps of the California capitol in Sacramento after UFW member Jose Campost Martinez, 25, died while spraying Parathion, a toxic pesticide. Chavez called on Governor George Deukmejian to ban Parathion immediately saying, "agribusiness and the agri-chemical industry reap their benefits. The workers bury their dead. That is not the way it should be". (4-2-90).
    - March for Justice, 1992 June
      Hundreds of grape and citrus workers have been walking off their jobs at farms across California's Coachella Valley in rotating daily demonstrations to protest low pay and rotten working conditions. Growers have frozen pay over six years, Farm Workers President Cesar Chavez said in leading a march on the Highway 111. (13-3-92).
    - Boycott the Grapes, 1988 January
      United Farm Workers President Cesar Chavez announced early this month that 15 consumer, environmental, and public health groups have joined the union's national "Wrath of Grapes" boycott and called for a ban on five pesticides used on table grapes. The coalition said it will ask 30 leading grocery chains to voluntarily support the Farm Workers campaign.
    - Solidarity with Farm Workers
      At storefront demonstration in Washington to press labor's boycott of California table grapes, UFW Vice President Arturo Rodriguez gets some enthusiastic support. From left, Newspaper Guild President Charles Dale; TNG office administrator Mary Aldrich; Ron Richardson, President of Hotel Employees and Restaurant Employees Local 25; TNG Secretary-Treasurer John Edgington; Josh Williams, President of the metropolitan Washington AFL-CIO, and Rodriguez. Dale, who participated in the UFW's "fast for life" campaign, called on union members to help ban five toxic pesticides used on California grapes. (40-4-88).
    - Passing the Cross
      Farm Workers President Cesar Chavez at Mass where he ended his 36-day "Fast for Life" passes small wooden cross to Rev. Jesse Jackson who then fasted fro three days. The continuing fast by trade unionists, clergy, and celebrities underscores the UFW's drive to ban the use of five toxic pesticides on California table grapes. The pesticides have caused deaths and illnesses among the farm worker families in the San Joaquin Valley. (36-4-88).
    - March on Washington